do you realize that that word anointed
means Messiah Cyrus was not the Messiah
he was he was called God's anointed but
what Cyrus wants to do would be a symbol
or a type of what Jesus Christ himself
was to do so he's a pastor what do you
mean
remember what Cyrus did Cyrus was going
to penetrate the domain of the enemy and
the way he was going to do it was by
descending into the deep just as Cyrus
Drive of the deep and descended as it
were and opened the gates
[Music]
so Jesus Christ the man who was being
crucified outside the city walls of
Jerusalem descended into the domain of
the enemy that in so-called impenetrable
domain dried up the deep in order to set
the captives free
[Music]
but wait there's more
because remember when when when when
Mouse's are sees this writing on the
wall this invisible hand part like the
words that were written were these it is
finished
your kingdom bounces off it's finished
it was the death knell and and walk
proud you know what I'm thinking about
right now when Christ died upon the
cross he cried out it is finished
[Music]